Contact

thangnv@hus.edu.vn

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyênthắng-trainer-b3bab5166 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Coaching
Executive Coaching
Life Coaching

Certifications

Communicating with Confidence (2015)

Building Trust
Igniting Emotional Engagement
Learning to Be Approachable
Amplifying Your Message Through

Powerful Framing and Storytelling

Nguyên Thắng Trainer

Coach | Trainer | HR Consult | HRBP | Story Telling Vĩnh Phúc, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

With over such experience in the field of People & Culture Development, Thang is a passionate and driven leader who strives to empower people and culture with his coaching, training and HR expertise. He is currently the Organizational & People Development Deputy Manager at Piaggio Group, a global leader in the people and culture sector, where he oversees the talent management, learning and development, and employer branding initiatives for the Asia Pacific region.

Thang is also a certified professional coach who specializes in emotional, life, leadership, and career coaching. He has helped numerous clients achieve their personal and professional goals, transformation, overcome challenges, and enhance their well-being and performance. He believes that coaching is a powerful tool to unlock the potential and creativity of individuals and teams, and to foster a culture of trust, collaboration, and innovation. His mission is to do things better by people inspiring, developing, learning, motivating, sharp and bold their life color.

Experience

Piaggio Group 6 years 11 months

ASIA Pacific Region P&OD Deputy Manager cum HR Business Partner for Piaggio Asia Pacific (Singapore)

November 2023 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

ASIA Pacific Region Organizational & People Development Deputy Manager

March 2023 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

ASIA Pacific Region Organizational & People Development Senior Supervisor

Page 1 of 3

July 2021 - March 2023 (1 year 9 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Resourcing & L&D Management
May 2020 - July 2022 (2 years 3 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Resourcing Management

May 2018 - March 2022 (3 years 11 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

ICF cum InCoach

Certified Professional Coach

January 2021 - September 2022 (1 year 9 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Star Engineering Inc

Former HR & GA Manager

July 2014 - April 2018 (3 years 10 months)

Vietnam

Eurocharm Group

Assistant Director Of Human Resources September 2013 - June 2014 (10 months)

Vietnam

Education

Emotional Coach | Life Coach | Leadership Coach | Career Coach

· (September 2019 - October 2020)

Training

· (October 2019 - October 2020)

Anphabe

Certificate, Building Winning Employer Brand · (2019 - 2019)

Vietnam National University, Hanoi

Bachelor's degree (2009 - 2013)

International coach federation

Coach, Emotional | Life | Leadership | Career Coach